# Daylan Hoff

**DevOps Engineer** 

#### Contact & Info

Salt Lake City, UT (435) 592-5991 daylan.hoff@gmail.com

Website:

www.daylanhoff.com

Linkedin: DaylanHoff

#### **Skills**

C++ C# .NET Framework **xUnit Powershell** Java **JUnit Python JavaScript NodeJS** ReactJS **Rest API RabbitMQ** Docker Ruby Groovy

Open VPN Google Cloud Outlook Azure Git Github Cloud Bees MySal Microsoft SQL **SQF MongoDB** Adobe Cloud **Photoshop** Illustrator Premiere Pro **After Effects Acrobats** 

#### **IDES**

Visual Studio VS Code RubyMine CLion PyCharm InteliJ Eclipse PhpStorm

#### **Environments**

Windows 7 - 11

MacOS

Linux

Linux Server

Amazon Workspace

CPanel

Plesk

VMware

Proxmox

# **Summary**

Extensive knowledge with multiple programming languages such as C#, C++, Java, .Net, Python, Node JS, and more. Experience working with and on technical support teams. Team leader effectively able to communicate with others and take charge of problems.

# **Work History**

06-2021 -Current

#### **DevOps Engineer**

AdvancedMD, South Jordan - Remote

- Wrote code with Powershell & .NET Frameworks to reduce time spent working with Git to help automate and improve life within the team.
- Utilized what is now known as Cloud Bees & Azure DevOps to effectively roll out product releases.
- Integrated team work skills in order to effectively communicate and produce quality tools with and for foreign and domestic departments.
- Worked with several other departments such as the Quality Assurance department in order to improve workflow and successfully achieve release goals.

04-2021-06/2021

# **Quality Assurance Engineer**

AdvancedMD, South Jordan - Remote

- Used Postman to test funtions of the application and reduce bugs.
- Created Unit Tests to help automate and reduce bugs while verifying the integrity of our application.
- Wrote code in the C# .NET Core Framework to implement the Unit Testing.
- Utilized a form of Agile Scrum to effectively communicate and plan with other members of the company.
- Worked with AWS Workspace, and servers to help setup, and automate the creation of other environments.

01-2019-03-2020

### Fullstack Developer

Neybyte Software, Seattle - Remote

- Trained Customer Support Agents regarding company operations, policies, and services to insure a customer satisfaction guarantee.
- Worked heavily with Customer Support to fix bugs, resulting in a 40% reduction in customer complains.
- Used Java to create the core front end and back end of the application.
- Utilized JUnit to properly test and validate our software helping to eliminate any issues before product launch.
- Scripted with MySQL and other programming languages like python to help query databases and gather data relevant to users.

#### Education

12-2021

# **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science**

Neumont College of Computer Science - Salt Lake City, UT